savethevideo.com 2019-07-12

# Privacy policy - SaveTheVideo.com

### Your privacy at SaveTheVideo.com (Last updated: 05/03/2019)

#### Privacy summary

You may use SaveTheVideo.com anonymously and without providing any personal information at all, but like most websites we collect non personally identifying information that are made available by web browsers and web servers and this information is only used to better understand how visitors use our website.

We also collect potentially personally identifying information like your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) for the purpose of limiting the usage of our services to prevent abuse and keep our services available to everyone.

We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the operation of our services and it's usually for a limited time only, we also don't share your personal information with anyone.

* * *

#### What information is collected ?

Some of the information that is collected on SaveTheVideo.com and used by third party services that we use:

  * IP address
  * Browser type
  * Date and time of each request
  * Referring site
  * Language preference

This information is stored temporarly in log files on our servers for a short time for the purpose of providing our services.

* * *

#### Cookies

Cookies are text files stored on your computer, SaveTheVideo.com uses cookies to provide advertising services, we also use third party services that make use of cookies to collect traffic data and provide advertising services.

We collect anonymous usage information on visitors to our site through the use of [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/) which may use tracking cookies to gather anonymous browser, operating system, geographic, and web site navigation information, to opt out of Google Analytics [Install Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

We provide advertisements through [MGID](https://www.mgid.com/), which uses cookies to identify a browser to show targeted ads, you can check out the [privacy and cookie policy](https://www.mgid.com/privacy-policy) page for more info, and you can use the opt-out button provided on the page to stop receiving targeted advertisements.

We provide advertisements through [PropellerAds](https://propellerads.com/), which uses cookies to deliver relevant advertisements, the Propeller Ads cookies do not collect personally identifiable information, you can check out the [privacy policy](https://propellerads.com/privacy/) page for more info, and you can opt-out using this [opt-out](https://propellerads.com/opt-out/) page.

We provide product recommendations through [DR MyCommerce, Inc. (Digital River, Inc.)](https://www.mycommerce.com/) or any of its subsidiaries, we are compensated for these recommendations whenever you make a purchase through our links at no additional cost to you, you can read more on the data collected by Digital River on their [privacy policy](https://www.mycommerce.com/privacy-policy/) page, you can also check out the opt-out options provided for you on the [Collection of Information, including Use of Cookies](https://www.mycommerce.com/privacy-policy/#collection_of_information,_including_use_of_cookies) section of the privacy policy.

* * *

#### Links

This website may contain links to other sites, please be aware that we are not responsible for the contents or privacy of such websites, you are encouraged to read the privacy policies of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

* * *

#### Privacy policy changes

SaveTheVideo.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, a notification will be posted clearly on our homepage for any major changes, the date of the last update will be shown on the top of the page, your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
